[English subtitles are available]
[الترجمة الإنجليزية متوفرة]
[The angle of the camera was off]
[كانت زاوية الكاميرا متوقفة]
[and didn't capture a front view of you.]
[ولم يلتقط منظر أمامي لك.]
[But the body scan check]
[لكن فحص فحص الجسم]
[will not miss your actions]
[لن تفوت أفعالك]
[and physical attributes.]
[والسمات الجسدية.]
[Will you be interested]
[هل ستهتم]
[to watch the clip one more time with me, Mr. Lin?]
[لمشاهدة المقطع مرة أخرى معي ، سيد لين؟]
[Let's see exactly what you did]
[دعنا نرى بالضبط ما فعلته]
[to Ye Tian on the night]
[إلى يي تيان في الليل]
[he was running tests]
[كان يجري الاختبارات]
[in the programming room.]
[في غرفة البرمجة.]
So that's what happened.
هذا ما حدث.
Zhang Hao Cheng and Lin Feng...
تشانغ هاو تشنغ ولين فنغ ...
This is wrong.
هذا خطأ.
We must make them pay for what they've done.
يجب أن نجعلهم يدفعون ثمن ما فعلوه.
Ms. Linda,
السيدة ليندا ،
let's make a copy of this file
لنقم بعمل نسخة من هذا الملف
and hand it to the police.
وتسليمها للشرطة.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
We're being hacked.
نحن نتعرض للاختراق.
Copy the file now.
انسخ الملف الآن.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
They're too fast.
إنها سريعة جدًا.
Let's see who hacked us.
دعونا نرى من اخترقنا.
So it is you.
لذا فهو أنت.
It could only be you.
يمكن أن تكون أنت فقط.
Yes!
نعم!
We finally beat those foreign rascals.
أخيرا تغلبنا على هؤلاء الأوغاد الأجانب.
Feels good.
اشعر براحة.
Not leaving behind a name after accomplishing a deed isn't my style.
عدم ترك اسم بعد إنجاز عمل ما ليس أسلوبي.
What about
ماذا عن
we leave a sign?
نترك علامة؟
Lin Feng,
لين فنغ ،
why did you do it?
لماذا قد قمت بفعلها؟
[Episode 33]
[الحلقة 33]
[Eight Hours]
[ثماني ساعات]
It's my turn.
انه دوري.
[Sent to Zhang Hao Cheng]
[مرسلة إلى Zhang Hao Cheng]
[Sending file]
[إرسال ملف]
[I only have to show the CCTV footage to the police]
[لا بد لي من عرض لقطات كاميرات المراقبة للشرطة فقط]
[and push all the blame onto you,]
[ودفع كل اللوم عليك ،]
[who do you think the police will believe?]
[من تعتقد أن الشرطة ستصدق؟]
Li.
لي.
Turn back home.
عد إلى المنزل.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
[You now have Zhang Hao Cheng's authorization.]
[لديك الآن إذن Zhang Hao Cheng.]
[Do you wish]
[هل تتمنى]
[to turn the GM 001]
[لتحويل GM 001]
[account]
[الحساب]
[into an NPC?]
[في NPC؟]
[Do you wish]
[هل تتمنى]
[to change GM 001's]
[لتغيير GM 001's]
[character name]
[اسم الشخصية]
[to Omen?]
[إلى الفأل؟]
[Do you wish to activate the new legendary story quest?]
[هل ترغب في تفعيل مهمة القصة الأسطورية الجديدة؟]
Xiao Tian,
شياو تيان
although I can't delete your account
على الرغم من أنني لا أستطيع حذف حسابك
nor find your coordinates,
ولا تجد إحداثياتك ،
I can still turn the whole Pangu
لا يزال بإمكاني قلب بانغو بأكملها
against you.
ضدك.
Ye Tian!
أيها تيان!
Bai Wei.
باي وي.
I'm so glad.
أنا جد مسرور.
I did it!
أنا فعلت هذا!
I've got the ID card access.
لقد حصلت على الوصول إلى بطاقة الهوية.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
I left the ID card on the table.
تركت بطاقة الهوية على الطاولة.
There's also breakfast.
يوجد أيضًا فطور.
Remember to eat it.
تذكر أن تأكله.
Will do.
سوف تفعل.
[Omen has descended.]
[نزل فأل.]
[The country is in danger.]
[البلد في خطر.]
[For the peace of the continent,]
[من أجل سلام القارة ،]
[warriors,]
[المحاربون،]
[rise up!]
[يرتفع!]
[Eliminate Omen]
[القضاء على الفأل]
[and you shall receive the highest honour]
[وستحصل على أعلى وسام]
[and reward]
[ومكافأة]
[ever given out in Pangu.]
[في أي وقت مضى في بانغو.]
What's that?
ما هذا؟
A world quest?
رحلة بحث عن العالم؟
This isn't in my plan.
هذا ليس في خطتي.
It doesn't fit Pangu's worldview.
إنه لا يتناسب مع نظرة بانغو للعالم.
Pretty interesting.
ممتع جدا.
Never mind it.
لا يهم.
Let us log out first
دعونا نسجل الخروج أولا
and deal with the 2021 error.
والتعامل مع خطأ 2021.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Oh, right.
صحيح.
You log out first.
عليك تسجيل الخروج أولا.
I'll wait for Xiao Liang
سأنتظر شياو ليانغ
so I can ask him if he's found it.
لذلك يمكنني أن أسأله عما إذا كان قد وجدها.
I'll keep you updated later.
سأبقيك على اطلاع في وقت لاحق.
Sounds good.
ًيبدو جيدا.
Brother.
أخ.
There's a problem.
هناك مشكلة.
I don't know whether I should tell you.
لا أعرف ما إذا كان علي إخبارك.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
[NPC Omen]
[NPC Omen]
Omen?
فأل؟
[Warriors,]
[المحاربون،]
[rise up!]
[يرتفع!]
[Eliminate Omen]
[القضاء على الفأل]
[and you shall receive...]
[وستتلقى ...]
Omen?
فأل؟
Isn't Pangu supposed to be a fantasy world?
أليس من المفترض أن يكون بانغو عالم خيالي؟
The name "Omen" sounds a little too sinister.
يبدو اسم "Omen" شريرًا جدًا.
[Come back.]
[عد.]
[We have a problem.]
[لدينا مشكلة.]
[Ye Tian's turned into Omen.]
[تحولت يي تيان إلى فأل.]
You carry on.
أنت تواصل.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
Wait.
انتظر.
Xiao Liang, where are you going?
شياو ليانغ ، إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
Are you going to kill Omen
هل ستقتل الفأل
and save the world?
وتنقذ العالم؟
Xiao Liang!
شياو ليانغ!
There's only
هناك فقط
one possibility.
احتمال واحد.
Lin Feng edited my code offline
قام Lin Feng بتحرير الكود الخاص بي في وضع عدم الاتصال
using
استخدام
the origin server.
الخادم الأصلي.
He turned me
أدارني
into an NPC.
في NPC.
So from now on,
لذا من الآن فصاعدًا ،
I've lost all the skills other players
لقد فقدت كل مهارات اللاعبين الآخرين
have access to.
الوصول الى.
That includes the Dual Skills.
يتضمن المهارات المزدوجة.
Doesn't that mean you've become everyone's enemy
لا يعني هذا أنك أصبحت عدوًا للجميع
and you're cornered?
وأنت محاصر؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
Ms. Wei!
السيدة وي!
I don't think the situation is that bad yet.
لا أعتقد أن الوضع بهذا السوء بعد.
On my way here,
في طريقي إلى هنا ،
I saw everybody heading away from Autumn City.
رأيت الجميع يتجهون بعيدًا عن مدينة الخريف.
That means his location
هذا يعني موقعه
hasn't been found.
لم يتم العثور عليها.
That's good.
هذا طيب.
As long as
طالما
they don't know where we are,
لا يعرفون أين نحن ،
we can continue to play cat and mouse.
يمكننا الاستمرار في لعب القط والفأر.
Look up there!
ننظر الى هناك!
Omen is inside.
فأل في الداخل.
Go in and take him down!
ادخل وانزله!
Invincible.
لا يقهر.
Hide behind the water vat.
اختبئ خلف وعاء الماء.
It's safer there.
إنه أكثر أمانًا هناك.
Where did you get this?
من اين حصلت على هذا؟
It's an Easter egg prop I saved.
إنها دعامة بيضة عيد الفصح التي أنقذتها.
He's in there!
إنه هناك!
Is this a joke?
هل هذه مزحه؟
Why is that thing in Pangu?
لماذا هذا الشيء في بانغو؟
Is Omen supposed to be
فهل من المفترض أن يكون
from another world?
من عالم آخر؟
Guys.
شباب.
Here to play with fire?
هنا للعب بالنار؟
Enough talking.
يكفي الحديث.
Get him!
اجلبه!
The game
اللعبة
has started.
بدأت.
Still alive, huh?
لا يزال على قيد الحياة ، أليس كذلك؟
Let's see how long you can hold out.
دعونا نرى كم من الوقت يمكنك الصمود.
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Mr. Lin,
السيد لين،
are you testing a new mission again?
هل تختبر مهمة جديدة مرة أخرى؟
I'd say this has to be the most interesting mission
أود أن أقول أن هذا يجب أن يكون المهمة الأكثر إثارة للاهتمام
in the history of Pangu.
في تاريخ بانغو.
Quick.
بسرعة.
Omen has to be in Autumn City.
Omen يجب أن يكون في مدينة الخريف.
Search the area.
ابحث في المنطقة.
This is a world quest!
هذه مهمة العالم!
Make haste.
جعل التسرع.
Move it.
حركه.
Search!
بحث!
Find him.
قم باجاده.
Ladies and gentlemen,
سيداتي سادتي،
I am Wild Boar.
أنا خنزير بري.
I've brought 150 men to search the street.
أحضرت 150 رجلاً لتفتيش الشارع.
Omen has to be here.
فأل يجب أن يكون هنا.
Show us your support.
أظهر لنا دعمك.
Allow Wild Boar to show you
اسمح للخنزير البري أن يظهر لك
an earth-shattering performance.
أداء مذهل.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
I had a dream
كان لدي حلم
about a similar scenario in the past.
حول سيناريو مشابه في الماضي.
You dreamed of being chased?
حلمت بأنك مطارد؟
No.
لا.
I dreamed that you and I were hiding in the bushes.
حلمت بأنك وأنا كنا مختبئين في الأدغال.
We weren't talking.
لم نكن نتحدث.
We were just quietly staring at the sky.
كنا نحدق بهدوء في السماء.
When did you
متى فعلت
have this dream?
هل لديك هذا الحلم؟
I'm not telling you.
أنا لا أقول لك.
Could it be the first time we met?
هل يمكن أن تكون هذه هي المرة الأولى التي التقينا فيها؟
You're so annoying.
انت مزعج جدا.
Don't be ridiculous.
لا تكن سخيفا.
I'm not a hopeless romantic.
أنا لست رومانسية ميؤوس منها.
Search the place properly!
ابحث في المكان بشكل صحيح!
Make sure
تأكد
you check
انت تفحص
every one of the NPC's stores.
كل واحد من متاجر NPC.
You keep telling me to be careful.
أنت تخبرني باستمرار أن أكون حذرا.
But you don't seem scared at all.
لكن لا يبدو أنك خائف على الإطلاق.
I am scared.
انا خائف.
I want nothing more than to get out of here alive
لا أريد شيئًا أكثر من الخروج من هنا حياً
so that I can be with you forever.
حتى أكون معك إلى الأبد.
We will.
سنقوم.
You know what?
أتعلم؟
Actually, there are many things
في الواقع ، هناك أشياء كثيرة
I didn't tell you.
لم اقول لكم.
To me, each day I am alive
بالنسبة لي ، أنا على قيد الحياة كل يوم
in Pangu
في بانغو
is a miracle.
معجزة.
I should've died a long time ago
كان يجب أن أموت منذ زمن طويل
in the testing cabin accident.
في حادث كابينة الاختبار.
But I somehow survived
لكنني نجوت بطريقة ما
by coincidence.
عن طريق الصدفة.
And I met you.
و قابلتك.
I suppose this is destiny.
أفترض أن هذا هو القدر.
I always wonder,
أتساءل دائما،
if that accident hadn't happened,
إذا لم يحدث هذا الحادث ،
would we have taken notice
كنا قد لاحظنا
of each other like this?
من بعضها البعض مثل هذا؟
If I could go back to that night,
إذا كان بإمكاني العودة إلى تلك الليلة ،
what choice should I make?
ما هو الاختيار الذي يجب علي فعله؟
Now I've finally got an answer.
الآن حصلت على إجابة أخيرًا.
If I could go back to that night,
إذا كان بإمكاني العودة إلى تلك الليلة ،
I would still enter the testing cabin
ما زلت أدخل مقصورة الاختبار
that would malfunction
من شأنه أن يعطل
without a second thought.
بدون تردد.
Not for anything else.
ليس لأي شيء آخر.
But just so I could meet you,
لكن فقط لأتمكن من مقابلتك ،
fall in love with you
وقعت في حبك
and be with you.
وكوني معك.
Even if our ending may not end up perfect,
حتى لو لم تكن نهايتنا مثالية ،
it's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Because every second and minute
لأن كل ثانية ودقيقة
I'm with you
أنا معك
is worth it.
انه يستحق ذلك.
Can... Cannibal.
يمكن ... أكلة لحوم البشر.
Omen is here.
فأل هنا.
Omen is right here!
فأل هنا!
Run!
يركض!
Xiao Liang, over here.
شياو ليانغ ، هنا.
Quick!
بسرعة!
Where are the men?
اين الرجال؟
Come on.
تعال.
Omen is here.
فأل هنا.
After him!
بعده!
Ye Tian,
يي تيان ،
where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
Look for someone at Love Flower Village.
ابحث عن شخص ما في Love Flower Village.
That's the only way out.
هذا هو السبيل الوحيد للخروج.
Why?
لماذا؟
You mean...
أنت تعني...
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
We'll look for the quack master.
سنبحث عن سيد الدجال.
Charge!
تهمة. شحن. يحاسب!
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Hurry!
عجل!
Omen and his bodyguards are injured.
فأل وحراسه أصيبوا.
After them!
بعدهم!
Victory will be ours!
سيكون النصر لنا!
[Big news.]
[أخبار كبيرة.]
[The bodyguards are players.]
[الحراس الشخصيون لاعبون.]
[They've chosen]
[لقد اختاروا]
[to align themselves with Omen.]
[لتتواءم مع فأل.]
[Finally, we managed to surround them]
[أخيرًا ، تمكنا من محاصرتهم]
at Love Flower Village.
في قرية زهرة الحب.
A final showdown will determine who wins and loses.
المواجهة النهائية ستحدد من سيفوز ومن يخسر.
He's not here.
انه ليس هنا.
Where is the village chief?
أين رئيس القرية؟
Isn't the chief right there?
أليس الرئيس هناك؟
Chief.
رئيس.
You have a visitor.
لديك زائر.
You're the village chief?
أنت رئيس القرية؟
Oh, Lin Feng.
أوه ، لين فنغ.
You really went to great lengths
لقد بذلت جهودًا كبيرة حقًا
in order to deal with me.
من أجل التعامل معي.
You actually modified the infrastructure of the server without permission.
لقد قمت بالفعل بتعديل البنية الأساسية للخادم دون إذن.
It's fine if I die.
لا بأس إذا مت.
But are you really
لكن هل أنت حقا
going to screw up Pangu?
ذاهب إلى إفساد بانغو؟
Surrender.
يستسلم.
Chase them! Stop running!
مطاردتهم!  توقف عن الركض!
Quick!
بسرعة!
Over here.
هنا.
This way. Quick!
من هنا.  بسرعة!
Freeze!
تجمد!
Stop.
قف.
Did you find the village chief?
هل وجدت رئيس القرية؟
Lin Feng modified the server.
قام لين فنغ بتعديل الخادم.
The whole NPC world
العالم كله NPC
has been messed up.
تم العبث بها.
We are surrounded by enemies.
نحن محاطون بالأعداء.
What should we do then?
ماذا يجب ان نفعل بعد ذلك؟
One word.
كلمه واحده.
Run!
يركض!
Stop running!
توقف عن الركض!
[Love Flower Village has only one exit.]
[قرية زهرة الحب لديها مخرج واحد فقط.]
[Xiao Tian,]
[شياو تيان]
[why did you choose a dead end?]
[لماذا اخترت طريق مسدود؟]
Stop!
قف!
What's the matter?
ما الأمر؟
What is it, Wei Wei?
ما هذا يا وي وي؟
Promise me.
اوعدني.
Make sure you live no matter what.
تأكد من أنك تعيش مهما كان الأمر.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Xiao Liang, keep him safe.
شياو ليانغ ، حافظ على سلامته.
Take him away.
يأخذه بعيدا.
Ms. Wei.
السيدة وي.
I won't go.
لن اذهب.
I'm not going.
أنا لن أذهب.
Go!
اذهب!
Bai Wei.
باي وي.
Hurry. You need to log out.
عجل.  تحتاج إلى تسجيل الخروج.
Go!
اذهب!
Wei Wei!
وي وي!
Let's go!
لنذهب!
Hurry! Don't lose them!
عجل!  لا تفقدهم!
Chase them!
مطاردتهم!
Charge!
تهمة. شحن. يحاسب!
Attack!
هجوم!
Bai Wei.
باي وي.
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
[You're physically fatigued.]
[أنت متعب جسديًا.]
[For your safety,]
[من أجل سلامتك]
[you have been disconnected.]
[لقد تم قطع الاتصال.]
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
[You're physically fatigued.]
[أنت متعب جسديًا.]
[Please take a rest before attempting to log in again.]
[يرجى أخذ قسط من الراحة قبل محاولة تسجيل الدخول مرة أخرى.]
[Pangu is good,]
[بانغو جيد ،]
[but your health is more important.]
[لكن صحتك أكثر أهمية.]
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
Let me connect.
دعني أتصل.
Ready.
مستعد.
One, two, three, push!
واحد ، اثنان ، ثلاثة ، ادفع!
Does the Black Wind Cave
هل كهف الريح السوداء
have another exit?
هل لديك مخرج آخر؟
All the exits have been blocked.
تم إغلاق جميع المخارج.
How could you still be so unfazed?
كيف يمكن أن تظل غير منزعج؟
What did you promise Ms. Wei?
ماذا وعدت السيدة وي؟
You have to stay alive.
عليك أن تبقى على قيد الحياة.
Xiao Liang,
شياو ليانغ
if I can't get out,
إذا لم أستطع الخروج ،
there's something
هناك شيء ما
I'd like you to relay to Bai Wei for me.
أود منك أن تنقل إلي باي وي.
One, two, three, push!
واحد ، اثنان ، ثلاثة ، ادفع!
Kill Omen! Go for it!
اقتل فأل!  أذهب خلفها !
Go for it!
أذهب خلفها !
Mr. Lin.
السيد لين.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I was wondering
كنت أتساءل
when you'd come to see me.
عندما تأتي لرؤيتي.
Lin Feng,
لين فنغ ،
I came to urge you to turn yourself in.
جئت لأحثك على تسليم نفسك.
Just stop.
توقف.
It's not too late.
لم يفت الوقت بعد.
Turn myself in?
تسليم نفسي؟
If I did that,
إذا فعلت ذلك ،
what would happen to Celeste?
ماذا سيحدث لسيليست؟
What would happen to Pangu?
ماذا سيحدث لبانغو؟
If you listened to the voice recording,
إذا استمعت إلى التسجيل الصوتي ،
you should know that
عليك ان تعلم ذلك
it wasn't my intention.
لم تكن نيتي.
I did do some wrong things.
فعلت بعض الاشياء الخاطئة
But I did them for a reason.
لكنني فعلتها لسبب ما.
Don't you see?
ألا ترى؟
Stop deceiving yourself.
توقف عن خداع نفسك.
This contains records of all the crimes
هذا يحتوي على سجلات لجميع الجرائم
you and Zhang Hao Cheng had committed.
لقد ارتكبت أنت و Zhang Hao Cheng.
It also recorded
كما سجلت
what you just said.
ماذا قلت للتو.
This
هذه
is the real reason you came, right?
هو السبب الحقيقي لمجيئك ، أليس كذلك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Because you removed the footage.
لأنك أزلت اللقطات.
I need new evidence.
أنا بحاجة إلى أدلة جديدة.
Lin Feng,
لين فنغ ،
I'm begging you.
أتوسل إليك.
Give yourself a chance.
امنح نفسك فرصة.
I don't want to be the one to send you to prison.
لا أريد أن أكون الشخص الذي يرسلك إلى السجن.
A signal jammer.
جهاز تشويش إشارة.
As for the criminal evidence in that thing,
أما الدليل الجنائي في ذلك الشيء ،
the jammer would've damaged it too.
جهاز التشويش سيتلفه أيضًا.
In this room,
في هذه الغرفة،
voice recording will not work.
التسجيل الصوتي لن يعمل.
Thanks for your goodwill.
شكرا على حسن نيتك.
But I have disappointed you.
لكني أصبت بخيبة أمل.
I want to quit.
أريد أن الإقلاع عن التدخين.
Approved.
وافق.
[Mr. Lin, please.]
[السيد.  لين ، من فضلك.]
[This place is much bigger than I thought.]
[هذا المكان أكبر بكثير مما كنت أعتقد.]
[Yeah.]
[نعم.]
[Your office looks really imposing.]
[يبدو مكتبك مهيبًا حقًا.]
[Let's put our photo right here.]
[لنضع صورتنا هنا.]
[Linda,]
[ليندا،]
[submit the meeting minutes to me.]
[أرسل محضر الاجتماع إلي.]
[Will do.]
[سوف تفعل.]
[Linda.]
[ليندا.]
[I think,]
[أظن،]
[now that we're here,]
[الآن بعد أن وصلنا ،]
[we have to accomplish something big.]
[علينا أن ننجز شيئًا كبيرًا.]
[Don't you agree?]
[ألا توافق؟]
[Yes.]
[نعم.]
[And I believe]
[وأعتقد]
[you can do it.]
[يمكنك أن تفعل ذلك.]
[So can you.]
[لذا يمكنك أنت.]
[Right.]
[الصحيح.]
[Celeste Group]
[مجموعة سيليست]
Hello, Ms. Linda.
مرحبا سيدة ليندا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
All the best.
أتمنى لك كل خير.
Where is Ms. Linda off to?
إلى أين السيدة ليندا؟
Hello.
مرحبًا.
This is my resume.
هذه سيرتي الذاتية.
Hi.
أهلاً.
Your photograph is not suitable.
صورتك غير مناسبة.
Please change to another.
الرجاء التغيير لآخر.
What photo?
ما الصورة؟
A two-inch photo.
صورة بحجم بوصتين.
And you've already been hired.
وقد تم تعيينك بالفعل.
You can go to HR to report in.
يمكنك الذهاب إلى الموارد البشرية لتقديم تقرير في.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[Goodbye,]
[مع السلامة،]
[Celeste.]
[سيليست.]
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Omen is dead.
فأل ميت.
[Black Wind Cave]
[كهف الرياح السوداء]
Search, GM 001.
بحث GM 001.
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
[The user does not exist.]
[المستخدم غير موجود.]
No, it's not that.
لا ، ليس هذا.
Search, Omen.
بحث فأل.
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
[The user does not exist.]
[المستخدم غير موجود.]
Search...
بحث...
Search for Ye Tian.
ابحث عن يي تيان.
[Sorry.]
[آسف.]
[The user does not exist.]
[المستخدم غير موجود.]
Delete the mission.
احذف المهمة.
Delete all records of my modification.
حذف كافة سجلات تعديلي.
[Mission deleted.]
[تم حذف المهمة.]
[Data restored.]
[استعادة البيانات.]
[NPC Omen]
[NPC Omen]
[has been changed back to player]
[تم تغييره مرة أخرى إلى لاعب]
[GM 001.]
[GM 001.]
[All traces of modification have been deleted.]
[تم حذف كافة آثار التعديل.]
[Tonight at 11.50pm.]
[الليلة الساعة 11.50 مساءً.]
[Click to read]
[انقر للقراءة]
[New message received]
[تم استلام رسالة جديدة]
[Bring target information and deposit]
[جلب معلومات الهدف والإيداع]
[Tonight at 11.50 pm, meet at the south gate of Binhai Park. Wear red.]
[الليلة في تمام الساعة 11.50 مساءً ، التقينا عند البوابة الجنوبية لحديقة بينهاى.  لبس احمر.]
That was fun.
كان هذا ممتعا.
Wait for me.
الانتظار لي.
A good dog doesn't block the path.
الكلب الجيد لا يسد الطريق.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Don't push your luck, buddy.
لا تضغط على حظك يا صديقي.
Luck?
حظ؟
Luck, you say?
الحظ ، كما تقول؟
Do I not have luck?
هل ليس لدي حظ؟
I'll give you luck.
سأعطيك الحظ.
Get up.
استيقظ.
I don't give a damn about luck!
أنا لا أبالي بالحظ!
Your luck.
حظك.
Wimp.
ضعيف.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Boss,
رئيس،
it's been arranged.
تم الترتيب له.
The flight is at 6am tomorrow.
الرحلة في الساعة 6 صباحًا غدًا.
All your assets
كل ما تبذلونه من الأصول
have been transferred to overseas accounts.
تم تحويلها إلى حسابات خارجية.
Are you really okay
هل أنت بخير حقا
with leaving like this?
بمغادرة مثل هذا؟
You're just going
أنت فقط ذاهبة
to hand Celeste over to that rascal, Lin Feng?
لتسليم سيليست لهذا الوغد ، لين فنغ؟
I'm not handing it over.
أنا لا أسلمها.
I'm dumping it.
أنا ألقي به.
The Celeste right now
سيليست الآن
has become nothing but a burden.
أصبح لا شيء سوى عبء.
Burden?
حرج؟
Why else would I leave?
وإلا لماذا سأرحل؟
Did you really think
هل فكرت حقا
it was because Lin Feng had dirt on me?
كان ذلك لأن لين فنغ كان لديه الأوساخ؟
Having dirt on someone is a two-edged sword.
وجود وسخ على شخص ما هو سيف ذو حدين.
Either party could end up getting hurt.
يمكن أن يتأذى أي من الطرفين.
That's not what I'm worried about at all.
هذا ليس ما أنا قلق بشأنه على الإطلاق.
What worries me is the news I got today.
ما يقلقني هو الأخبار التي تلقيتها اليوم.
The 2021 code error
خطأ رمز 2021
is becoming worse.
أصبح أسوأ.
Didn't we already set up a secret team
ألم نشكل فريقًا سريًا بالفعل
to resolve the bug?
لحل الخلل؟
Today, the head representative told me
اليوم ، قال لي رئيس مندوب
that the 2021 code error
أن خطأ رمز 2021
has attached itself onto the origin server.
قام بإرفاق نفسه بخادم الأصل.
There's nothing else they can do.
لا يوجد شيء آخر يمكنهم فعله.
That means
هذا يعني
Pangu is...
Pangu هي ...
It's hopeless.
انها ميؤوس منها.
The Pangu right now
البانجو الآن
is like a ticking time bomb.
مثل قنبلة موقوتة.
The countdown has started.
بدأ العد التنازلي.
It could explode any time.
يمكن أن تنفجر في أي وقت.
The only thing we can do
الشيء الوحيد الذي يمكننا القيام به
is to stay far away from it.
هو الابتعاد عنها.
Boss,
رئيس،
I'll get Yun Er to pack her things then.
سأجعل Yun Er يحزم أغراضها بعد ذلك.
Is this karma?
هل هذه الكرمة؟
Yun Er.
يون ار.
Open the door.
افتح الباب.
Yes.
نعم.
Yun Er.
يون ار.
Yun Er?
يون ار؟
I kept telling you all
ظللت أخبركم جميعا
to keep her in your sight at all times.
لإبقائها في عينيك في جميع الأوقات.
Don't you know what keeping her in your sight means?
ألا تعرف ماذا يعني إبقائها في عينيك؟
You couldn't even watch a girl.
لا يمكنك حتى مشاهدة فتاة.
Are you people trash?
هل أنتم الناس القمامة؟
Sorry, boss.
آسف يا رئيس.
Sorry?
آسف؟
Go and find her!
اذهب وابحث عنها!
Scram!
انصرف!
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
Boss,
رئيس،
don't fret.
لا تأكل.
I checked the surveillance cameras.
راجعت كاميرات المراقبة.
Yun Er made a rope
صنع يون إر حبل
using the bed sheet
باستخدام ملاءة السرير
and escaped by herself.
وهربت بنفسها.
I thought she had been taken.
اعتقدت أنها قد تم أخذها.
Oh no.
أوه لا.
She must have gone to look for Lin Feng.
لابد أنها ذهبت للبحث عن لين فنغ.
Help!
يساعد!
Is anyone there?
هل من أحد هناك؟
Anyone?
أي واحد؟
Who are you?
من أنت؟
Say something.
قل شيئا.
It's no use.
غير صالح.
The more you struggle, the tighter it gets.
كلما كافحت ، كلما ازدادت صرامة.
It'll slowly cut off your blood circulation.
سوف يقطع الدورة الدموية ببطء.
Your hands will be crippled.
ستصاب يديك بالشلل.
You just want money, right?
أنت فقط تريد المال ، أليس كذلك؟
How much do you want?
كم تريد؟
I'll give it to you.
سأعطيك إياها.
More money than you'll ever need.
أموال أكثر مما تحتاجه.
To answer your first question,
للإجابة على سؤالك الأول ،
I'm not a killer.
أنا لست قاتلاً.
And you didn't simply come into contact with me.
وأنت لم تتواصل معي ببساطة.
I've intercepted all the information
لقد اعترضت كل المعلومات
going in and out of your house.
الدخول والخروج من منزلك.
So your only choice is me,
لذا خيارك الوحيد هو أنا
Mr. Zhang Yun Er.
السيد تشانغ يون عير.
Why...
لماذا...
Why are you doing this?
لماذا تفعل هذا؟
The second question.
السؤال الثاني.
I didn't kidnap you for money.
أنا لم أختطفك من أجل المال.
It's because of your dad, Zhang Hao Cheng.
إنه بسبب والدك ، Zhang Hao Cheng.
There's a debt
هناك دين
he has to pay.
عليه أن يدفع.
But don't worry.
لكن لا تقلق.
Nothing will happen to you.
لا شيء سوف يحدث لك.
I made a promise to someone.
لقد قطعت وعدًا لشخص ما.
I won't put other people in danger
لن أضع الآخرين في خطر
just to get revenge on Zhang Hao Cheng.
فقط للانتقام من Zhang Hao Cheng.
You kidnapped me
لقد اختطفتني
so you could bait him?
لذلك يمكنك أن تطعمه؟
How did you even think of that?
كيف فكرت في ذلك؟
Zhang Hao Cheng only cares
تشانغ هاو تشنغ يهتم فقط
about himself.
عن نفسه.
You think he'd walk into danger to save me?
هل تعتقد أنه سيمشي في خطر لينقذني؟
Stop dreaming.
توقف عن الحلم.
Humans tend to do
يميل البشر إلى فعل ذلك
unpredictable things
أشياء لا يمكن التنبؤ بها
when they're caught in extraordinary circumstances.
عندما يتم القبض عليهم في ظروف غير عادية.
Hunting Dog.
كلب صيد.
[In one hour.]
[في ساعة واحدة.]
Nanyuan Warehouse.
مستودع نانيوان.
Come alone.
تعال وحدك.
[Help!]
[يساعد!]
[Let me go!]
[دعني أذهب!]
2021.
2021.
Did you come to jeer at me too?
هل جئت للسخرية مني أيضا؟
Did you see Ye Tian?
هل رأيت يي تيان؟
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Ms. Wei.
السيدة وي.
What's wrong with you, Ms. Wei?
ما خطبك يا سيدة وي؟
Ye Tian is still alive.
يي تيان لا يزال على قيد الحياة.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I said, Ye Tian is alive.
قلت ، يي تيان على قيد الحياة.
[Xiao Liang,]
[شياو ليانغ]
[there's something]
[هناك شيء ما]
[I'd like you to relay to Bai Wei for me.]
[أود منك أن تنقل إلى باي وي من أجلي.]
[I have a bad memory.]
[لدي ذاكرة سيئة.]
[Whatever you wish to say,]
[أيًا كان ما ترغب في قوله ،]
[you can tell her yourself after we fight a way out of here.]
[يمكنك إخبارها بنفسك بعد أن نقاتل في سبيل الخروج من هنا.]
[What's that sound?]
[ما هذا الصوت؟]
[Go and check.]
[اذهب وتحقق.]
[Freedom?]
[حرية؟]
[You went to Love Flower Village]
[ذهبت إلى قرية زهرة الحب]
[to look for him, right?]
[للبحث عنه ، أليس كذلك؟]
[Yes.]
[نعم.]
[That's him.]
[انه هو.]
[What do you need him for?]
[ما الذي تريده منه؟]
[Because there's a method worth trying.]
[لأن هناك طريقة تستحق المحاولة.]
[But it's very risky.]
[لكنها مخاطرة كبيرة.]
[Cut the crap.]
[قطع الفضلات.]
[I promised Ms. Wei to protect you.]
[لقد وعدت السيدة وي أن تحميك.]
[It doesn't matter how.]
[لا يهم كيف.]
[Okay.]
[تمام.]
[Then let's ask for apprenticeship.]
[ثم دعنا نطلب التلمذة الصناعية.]
[Apprenticeship?]
[فترة التدريب في المهنة؟]
[From him?]
[منه؟]
[My dear apprentices.]
[أيها المتدربون الأعزاء.]
[I will teach you the Dual Skills.]
[سأعلمك المهارات المزدوجة.]
Dual Skills?
المهارات المزدوجة؟
You...
أنت...
How can two men learn the Dual Skills?
كيف يمكن لرجلين تعلم المهارات المزدوجة؟
Ye Tian said
قال يي تيان
his NPC status
وضعه في المجلس الوطني لنواب الشعب
at that time
في ذلك الوقت
did not have gender detection.
لم يكن لديك الكشف عن الجنس.
So Freedom wasn't able to determine
لذلك لم تكن Freedom قادرة على تحديد ذلك
whether he's a man or woman.
سواء كان رجلا أو امرأة.
To Freedom,
من أجل الحرية،
Ye Tian could be a female.
يمكن أن تكون يي تيان أنثى.
So,
وبالتالي،
you two logged out after learning the skill.
قمتما بتسجيل الخروج بعد تعلم المهارة.
The players thought Omen had died
اعتقد اللاعبون أن Omen قد مات
and disappeared.
واختفى.
Yes.
نعم.
Then I got out
ثم خرجت
of the cave together with the crowd.
الكهف مع الحشد.
Ms. Wei,
السيدة وي
I've successfully completed
لقد أكملت بنجاح
that task you have given me, right?
تلك المهمة التي كلفتموني بها ، أليس كذلك؟
Good work, Xiao Liang.
عمل جيد ، شياو ليانغ.
Ms. Wei,
السيدة وي
be gentle.
كن لطيفآ.
I only have one life right now.
لدي حياة واحدة فقط الآن.
If you hit me too hard and killed me,
إذا ضربتني بشدة وقتلتني ،
that's two lives in one.
هذا يعيشان في واحد.
Sorry about that.
اسف بشأن ذلك.
My mistake.
غلطتي.
So,
وبالتالي،
where did you guys log out from?
من أين خرجتم يا رفاق؟
Take me there.
خذني هناك.
Come.
اتى.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
your dad will come?
سوف يأتي والدك؟
If he does come,
إذا جاء ،
what are you going to do?
ماالذي ستفعله؟
Kill him.
اقتله.
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
What kind of deep grievance
أي نوع من التظلم العميق
do you have with each other?
هل لديكم مع بعضكم البعض؟
A life for a life is all.
الحياة من أجل الحياة هي كل شيء.
Could there be some kind of misunderstanding?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك نوع من سوء الفهم؟
Zhang Hao Cheng isn't a saint.
Zhang Hao Cheng ليس قديسا.
But,
لكن،
he wouldn't go as far as kill someone.
لن يذهب إلى حد قتل شخص ما.
Of course he wouldn't kill someone himself.
بالطبع لن يقتل شخصًا بنفسه.
People like you
أناس مثلك
always keep your hands clean.
دائما ابق يديك نظيفة.
Because you get people like me to do your dirty work.
لأنك تجعل الناس مثلي يقومون بعملك القذر.
Am I right?
هل انا على حق؟
Then...
ثم...
Who...
من...
Who did he kill?
من قتل؟
He sent someone
أرسل شخص ما
to kill the only person
لقتل الشخص الوحيد
I cared about in this world.
اهتممت بهذا العالم.
Why?
لماذا؟
That's what I'd like to know too.
هذا ما أود أن أعرفه أيضًا.
This means
هذا يعنى
he knows
هو يعرف
it's you who have kidnapped me?
أنت من خطفتني؟
Then he won't come.
ثم لن يأتي.
Boss,
رئيس،
it's another 30km to the airport.
إنها تبعد 30 كم أخرى عن المطار.
You can take a rest first.
يمكنك أن تأخذ قسطا من الراحة أولا.
I'll call you when we're there.
سأتصل بك عندما نكون هناك.
Drive faster.
محرك أسرع.
Okay.
تمام.
Are you sure it's okay for him to log in like this?
هل أنت متأكد من أنه لا بأس به في تسجيل الدخول بهذه الطريقة؟
What if he
ماذا لو كان
becomes another "public enemy no. 1"?
يصبح آخر "عدو عام رقم 1"؟
I'll get him to log out
سأجعله يسجل الخروج
if there's any trouble.
إذا كان هناك أي مشكلة.
Talking about logging out,
نتحدث عن تسجيل الخروج ،
I think the duration limit
أعتقد أن الحد الأقصى للمدة
to be online was removed today.
أن تكون متصلاً بالإنترنت تمت إزالته اليوم.
Because Lin Feng tampered with
لأن لين فنغ عبث
the base structure of Pangu's server.
الهيكل الأساسي لخادم Pangu.
Are you alright?
هل انت بخير؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'm fine.
أنا بخير.
It turned out to be a blessing in disguise.
اتضح أنها نعمة مقنعة.
The monitoring system can't detect me now.
لا يمكن لنظام المراقبة الكشف عني الآن.
Really?
هل حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
But I'm not sure
ولكني لست متأكدا
how long this situation will last.
إلى متى سيستمر هذا الوضع.
We still have to hurry.
لا يزال يتعين علينا الإسراع.
Wei Wei,
وي وي ،
I want to go to Celeste.
أريد أن أذهب إلى سيليست.
Right now?
فى الحال؟
Yes, now.
نعم الآن.
I don't want to wait another minute.
لا أريد أن أنتظر دقيقة أخرى.
Xiao Liang,
شياو ليانغ
I need you to find more people
أريدك أن تجد المزيد من الناس
to install surveillance.
لتثبيت المراقبة.
Try to cover
حاول التستر
the whole Pangu.
بانغو كله.
Then we'll be able to determine
ثم سنكون قادرين على تحديد
where the mosaic is
حيث الفسيفساء
so that we can hunt it down
حتى نتمكن من تعقبها
and get rid of it.
والتخلص منه.
This is also the only way to resolve
هذه أيضًا هي الطريقة الوحيدة للحل
the 2021 error.
خطأ 2021.
Okay,
تمام،
I'll get it done.
سوف أنجزها.
Stay safe.
ابق آمنًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Wei Wei,
وي وي ،
we will soon
سنقوم قريبا
meet in the real world.
يجتمع في العالم الحقيقي.
I'll be waiting.
سأكون بانتظار.
[42 days.]
[42 يومًا.]
[I was trapped inside for 42 days.]
[كنت محاصرًا بالداخل لمدة 42 يومًا.]
[42 days!]
[42 يومًا!]
[I've finally woken up.]
[لقد استيقظت أخيرًا.]
Yun Er.
يون ار.
[Looks like you don't know enough about a father.]
[يبدو أنك لا تعرف الكثير عن الأب.]
No!
لا!
[No matter how heartless he treats other people,]
[بغض النظر عن مدى قسوة معاملته للآخرين ،]
in his heart,
في قلبه،
there is always a soft spot.
هناك دائما بقعة ناعمة.
It's you, Zhang Yun Er.
إنه أنت ، Zhang Yun Er.
[We're best friends.]
[وكان أفضل أصدقاء.]
[Today]
[اليوم]
[is probably the last time we'd see each other.]
[ربما تكون آخر مرة نرى فيها بعضنا البعض.]